<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-04-08T16:56:00-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Diego S.C.</title><subtitle>{&quot;en&quot;=&gt;&quot;I'm a software, web and musician (why not) developer in new things.&quot;, &quot;pt&quot;=&gt;&quot;Sou dev de software, web e músico (por que não) em coisas novas.&quot;}</subtitle><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">The First of many to come!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/04/07/the-first-of-many-to-come.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The First of many to come!" /><published>2017-04-07T19:10:11-03:00</published><updated>2017-04-07T19:10:11-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2017/04/07/the-first-of-many-to-come</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2017/04/07/the-first-of-many-to-come.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;here-i-am-writing-my-first-of-many-post-that-will-come&quot;&gt;Here I am, writing my first of many post that will come&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everything in life has a beginning &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;captain obvious&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, this is mine begin, the begin to getting out of my box and get started to expose things that I did, I do and the things that I’ll do for this world, I spent all day thinking what am I going to writing about here in my first post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what I did was watching some Youtube channels, reading some Bleach mangas &lt;em&gt;“no, I’m not an otaku”&lt;/em&gt; and playing Grand Theft Auto V for long hours, after all, I bought the game on Steam pre-order and I haven’t finished the game since then.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Before all of that, I had already accomplished all household chore&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my free time in somewhere in my brain I was thinking about my first post content, I was thinking about it since the day I had that idea to create / build a blog came into my heart and it was working together with my mind, they Did not stop building, scheming, building and scheming whole of the idea that could be possible right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, this is a rainy friday, &lt;em&gt;april 07, 2017&lt;/em&gt;, are exactly 07h10 P.M and I’m here writing those random things to not push up to the server with an only &lt;em&gt;“about”&lt;/em&gt; page but at least one post page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here I do the honours to open my blog and I thank you if you are here for curiosity, idleness, sadness, happiness, &lt;strong&gt;you are very welcome to my blog&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Everything in life has a begining &quot;capitain obvious&quot;, this is mine begin, the begin to getting out of my box and get started to expose things that I did, I do and the things that I'll do for...</summary></entry><entry xml:lang="pt"><title type="html">O Primeiro de muitos!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2017/04/07/o-primeiro-de-muitos.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="O Primeiro de muitos!" /><published>2017-04-07T19:10:11-03:00</published><updated>2017-04-07T19:10:11-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2017/04/07/o-primeiro-de-muitos</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2017/04/07/o-primeiro-de-muitos.html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;aqui-estou-eu-escrevendo-meu-primeiro-de-muitos-post-que-hão-de-vir&quot;&gt;Aqui estou eu, escrevendo meu primeiro de muitos post que hão de vir&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Como tudo nessa vida tem um ínicio &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;capitão óbvio&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, esse é o meu ínicio, o ínicio de sair um pouco da minha caixa e começar expor as coisas que eu fiz, faço e pretendo fazer para esse mundo, passei o dia todo pensando no que escrever para o meu primeiro post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mas, tudo o que eu fiz foi assistir alguns canais no Youtube, ler alguns mangas do Bleach &lt;em&gt;“não, eu não sou otaku”&lt;/em&gt; e passar o resto da tarde jogando Grand Theft Auto V afinal, comprei esse jogo na pré-venda na Steam e até hoje eu não consegui finaliza-lo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Antes de tudo isso, eu já havia completado os afazeres de casa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Durante esse meu momento de lazer em algum lugar do meu cerebro estava eu pensando no primeiro conteúdo, estava pensando nesse primeiro post desde quando essa idéia de criar um blog surgiu no meu coração e em conjunto com a minha mente não paravam de construir, maquinar, construir e maquinar essa idéia para que ela fosse possível agora.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Então, em plena sexta-feira chuvosa, &lt;em&gt;07 de abril de 2017&lt;/em&gt;, são exatamente &lt;em&gt;19h10&lt;/em&gt; da noite estou eu aqui escrevendo coisas aleatórias para não subir esse blog para o servidor somente com uma página de “sobre” mas também com um primeiro post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daqui eu faço as honras de inaugurar meu blog e eu agradeço a você(s) que por curiosidade, por ociosidade, por tristeza ou felicidade, &lt;strong&gt;seja(m) mais que bem vindo ao meu blog&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Como tudo nessa vida tem um ínicio &quot;capitão óbvio&quot;, esse é o meu ínicio, de sair um pouco da minha caixa e começar expor as coisas que eu fiz, faço e pretendo fazer para...</summary></entry></feed>